Hey, welcome back. This just will be a short video to fix the right hand position when climbing up.
嘿，欢迎回来。这只是一个简短的视频，以解决爬升时右手的位置问题。
So one thing that's been bugging me is when we reach the ledge and try to climb up,
有一件事一直困扰着我，那就是当我们到达壁架并试图往上爬的时候、
the position of our right hand seems to be higher than the ledge.
我们的右手的位置似乎比壁架高。
And that's something that I like to fix before we move on. Since this will just be some simple
而这是我想在我们继续前进之前解决的问题。由于这只是一些简单的
adjustment, I'm going to directly do it inside of this animation sequence. So double click to open
调整，我将直接在这个动画序列中进行调整。所以双击来打开
this climb to top linked and inside of this skeleton tree here, I'm going to scroll down
在这个骨架树中，我将向下滚动到上臂R。
to this upper arm R. And first thing at the first frame, I'm going to click here to add new key.
首先在第一帧，我将点击这里添加新的键。
Then I'm going to scroll to the part when this right hand is reaching out
然后我将滚动到这个右手伸出来的部分
to grab something in the air. All right, somewhere near here. And I'm going to change its rotation
去抓空中的东西。好的，在这附近的某个地方。我将改变它的旋转
a little bit. So I'm going to rotate it a bit and this way and rotate it a bit and this way.
一点点。所以我要把它旋转一下，然后再这样旋转一下，再这样旋转一下。
And I'm going to click add the new key.
然后我将点击添加新键。
And try to preview it.
并尝试预览它。
Yeah, I think this will work. I'm going to see what this looks like in play.
是的，我认为这将是工作。我要看看在游戏中这是什么样子。
So try to climb up. Yeah, something like that.
所以试着爬上去。是的，类似这样的东西。
I think this is already something that we can use. Much better than the original look.
我想这已经是我们可以使用的东西了。比原来的样子好多了。
And
而且